JEREMY THIBEAU

22 Amroth Avenue, Toronto, ON, M4C 4H2 Phone: (506) 961-8852

Email: thibeau.jeremy@gmail.com

March 19, 2020

To whom it may concern,

Please accept the attached resume and this cover letter in application for the advertised position. My education at George Brown College has equipped me with the technical skills to succeed in this role, while my work in Service and Sales at Tangerine has given me experience with meeting deadlines and taking ownership of my work.

In my courses at George Brown College, I have worked with several different programming languages and tools to produce software solutions following the assigned requirements. Through these projects, I have used agile software development methodologies with a focus on object-oriented programming principles.

In my role as a Client Solutions Lead, I am part of a team that works with many departments within the bank and with our clients. Working with escalated client issues often requires time-sensitive follow-ups with clients. I take ownership of the situation, set expectations to the client for next steps, and follow through to provide an effective resolution. I often coordinate with the required departments to suggest process improvements or amendments to a company knowledge base in order to enhance the client and employee experience.

My ongoing education and previous work experience have given me the tools needed to thrive in this field. I am eager to build on the technical skills I have developed during my time at George Brown College, and to leverage my customer service experience at Tangerine. I look forward to meeting with you.

Sincerely,

Jeremy Thibeau

gospher

JEREMY THIBEAU

22 Amroth Avenue, Toronto, ON, M4C 4H2 Phone: (506) 961-8852

Email: thibeau.jeremy@gmail.com

PROFILE

Innovative thinker with a focus on problem solving and multi-tasking. Experience with client service in the financial industry, programming in multiple languages, and a background in teaching and mathematics. Adaptable, resourceful, and willing to take on challenges.

EDUCATION

George Brown College	2018 -	Computer Programmer Analyst Diploma
St. Thomas University	2014 2013	Bachelor of Education Bachelor of Arts, Major in Math, Minor in English & Psychology
Riverview High School	2009	New Brunswick Secondary School Diploma

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & SOFTWARE EXPERIENCE

- . C#
- Python
- SQL
- Java
- HTML
- JavaScript
- PHP

- GitHub
- Eclipse
- Angular
- · Visual Studio
- ASP.NET

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tangerine	2015 - 2015 2015 2014 - 2015	Client Solutions Lead Mortgage Specialist Savings Specialist Savings Associate
Brunswick News	2010 - 2014	Customer Service Representative

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

Bliss Carmen Middle School	2014	Teaching Internship, Science and Social Studies
Moncton High School	2013	Teaching Internship, Mathematics

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

George Brown College	2018-2019	Dean's List (4 semesters)
Tangerine	0	Top Mortgage Specialist, Quality Top Savings Associate, Quality

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.